Unknown are the names
of the flowers that have been trampled
Birds have fallen to the earth
and long for the wind
Prayers won't solve anything
Only the will to fight
can change the here and now!
O pigs who laugh at the resolve
to walk over corpses to move forward
Livestock complacency? False prosperity?
Give us the freedom of dying,
starving wolves!
The humiliation of being caged
is what triggers us to fight back
We hunters slaughter prey
beyond the castle walls,
consumed with surging bloodlust,
as our crimson bows and arrows
pierce scarlet holes into the twilight
The World the Girl Saw: The Struggle for Trost, Part 2
Hey!
Hey! What's wrong, Armin?!
Pull yourself together!
Hey!
Armin! Hey, Armin!
You with me?! You okay?!
Are you all right? Where's your squad?
Squad...?
Oh, man. Pull yourself together.
Why are you all by yourself?
Plus you're all wet and slimy...
What the hell happened?
You're so useless! Just die already!
- Whoa! Calm down, Armin!
- Damn it!
Where is everyone?!
Give it a rest, Conny.
They've been wiped out. All but him.
Shut up! Armin hasn't said anything!
Just look around. It's obvious.
We don't got any
more time to waste on him.
Why is he the only one who's okay?!
Beats me. Maybe they
thought he was a corpse?
It sucks that they
ran into multiple Titans
and that only this
underachiever made it out alive.
Eren and the others
worked hard for nothing.
You bitch...
Want me to make it
so you never talk again?!
Stop it, you two!
We're all shaken up here!
All our friends are suddenly
dying left and right!
It's natural we're upset!
That's my Christa!
Marry me when this is over!
Yeah...
She is clowning
around more than usual.
Anyways, we can't stay here.
Can you stand, Armin?!
I'm sorry for the trouble.
I'll rendezvous with the rearguard.
Hey...
Armin!
Let's go, Conny!
We've been ordered to advance!
This is hell...
No, it hasn't become hell.
I was just mistaken until now.
This world has always been hell,
from the very start.
The strong prey on the weak.
It's such a simple,
straightforward world.
It's just, my friends...
They tried to be strong in this world.
They helped me, someone who was weak.
I couldn't bear it...
They saw me as someone
who needed to be protected.
I wanted to live
in this world like them...
I wanted to be strong and stand
shoulder-to-shoulder with them...
And this is the result.
Because of me, Eren wound up...
Hanna...
What are you doing?
Armin! Help!
Franz isn't breathing!
I've tried resuscitating him
over and over and over...
...but it's not working!
It's dangerous down here, Hanna.
- You need to get on a roof...
- I can't just leave Franz like this!
You don't understand, Hanna...
Franz is...
Please... stop this...
I...
I can't take this anymore...
I can't...
H-Hey, now! Don't you guys
realize how bad the situation is?!
Yeah! That's why we're doin' this!
And if you guys wanna live,
you'll give us some damn help!
- The hell with that!
- It's gonna get stuck!
- Letting people through comes first!
- We're all gonna get eaten standing here!
- What are you doing, soldier?!
- Go get 'em!
B-But...
Just try it, small fry! I'm the boss
of this town's merchant association!
Uhh, err...
Who do you think pays for
the meals you soldiers shit out?!
Do you have the money to
provide for the soldiers in this town?!
Push, all of you!
This cargo's worth more than you
can earn in your entire measly lives!
Help, and you'll be rewarded!
It'll be okay.
Your dad's going to use his
cannons to make the Titans go away.
Mom.
Over there.
Push!
Push if you don't wanna die!
Stop! The children...!
Damn! Why is it ignoring us?!
It's an Abnormal!
No point trying to figure it out!
It's fast! Not even we
elites can catch up to it!
At this rate...!
What... are you doing?
Oh, perfect timing!
Get these guys to help me!
I'll make it worth your while!
My comrades are dying as we speak.
They're fighting and dying because
the citizens haven't finished evacuating.
Of course they are!
It's your duty to give your hearts
to defend the lives
and property of the people!
Don't go gettin' a big head now
that you freeloaders have somethin' to do
after a century of uselessness!
If you feel people dying for
other people is a matter of course,
then I'm sure you'll understand
that a single, precious life
can sometimes save
the lives of many as well.
Just you try it!
Your employer and I go way back!
One word from me and
he'll be all over your sorry ass!
How can a dead body talk?
Wait!
S-Sir!
Pull the cart out.
Thanks, lady!
You really saved the day.
You have our gratitude!
Good work taking it down,
Ackermann. Very impressive.
Thank you, Sir. However...
I'm afraid I inadvertently dulled
my blades during the attack.
I will be more careful next time.
Just what have
you had to live through...?
No, never mind.
Why am I reminded
of it at a time like this?
Finished!
Look, Mom!
Oh, you did a great job, Mikasa!
It's very nice!
This style of embroidery has
been passed down in our clan
from generation to generation.
When you have a child,
it'll be your turn to pass it on too!
How can I have a child?
Err, why don't you ask your father that?
Well, Dad?
Oh, uhh, I don't really know, either!
Oh, I know!
Dr. Jaeger will be here any minute!
Why don't we ask him?
Oh, that must be him!
Coming!
Mikasa?
Yes. She's about your age.
There aren't many children
in these parts, so try to get along.
That depends on how she acts...
Eren.
That attitude is why
you've only made one friend.
Are they not home?
Mr. Ackermann!
It's Jaeger!
Is anyone home?
What's wrong?
What is it, Dad?
Too late.
Eren.
Have you seen the girl..
Mikasa... anywhere nearby?
No.
I see...
I'll get the Military Police
and have them conduct a search!
You'll wait at the foot of the mountain.
Is that clear, Eren?!
Eren!
Hey. Are you sure she'll actually sell?
We even went and killed her
parents before running off with her...
Take a look at her face.
Looks nice, but she's
still just a kid. She ain't for me.
I'm not asking about your tastes.
She's an "Oriental."
There used to be different types
of humans, you see.
Long ago, some people
fled a place called the Orient
and sought refuge inside the walls.
She's the last descendant of that clan.
We're gonna take her to the
underground market in the capital
and auction her off to those old perverts.
All the other Orientals have died out,
so she'll go for a pretty hefty price.
Her old man didn't
look like an Oriental to me.
She ain't pureblooded.
That's right! The mom
was the really valuable one!
But you had to freak out and kill her!
I-I couldn't help it! She put up a fight!
That all you got
to say for yourself?! Huh?!
Dr. Jaeger!
We've been expecting...
Hello. Pardon the intrusion.
Just take it nice and easy,
unless you want
your head split open with this.
This broad's crazy!
Mikasa! Run!
Huh? M-Mom...
Hurry, Mikasa!
Uhh...
Dad...?
Damn it! I've had enough of your crap!
What the hell?!
I said only kill the dad!
Don't look at me!
She's the one who...!
Save your excuses! Go get the kid!
Huh?!
Hey.
You better behave yourself.
Or else... this!
Cold...
Excuse me...
Hold it, kid!
How did you find this place?!
Err, uhh...
I got lost in the forest,
and then, umm, I saw a cabin, so...
You know kids shouldn't
wander around the forest all alone.
Scary wolves live
in the forest, you know.
But there's nothing to
worry about now.
We'll be happy to take you...
Thanks, Mister.
I already know the score.
So die, you asshole!
Huh?! What the hell?!
G-Get back here, kid!
You damn animal...!
Die! Die!
This is what you get!
This is what you deserve!
Never get up again!
You're safe now...
You can relax.
I take it you're Mikasa?
I'm Eren.
I'm Dr. Jaeger's son.
I'm sure you've met my dad before.
I was tagging along when he
visited your house for a checkup.
But then...
There were three of them.
Was it you?
Was it you who killed 'em?!
Was it?!
I'm gonna kill you!
F-Fight!
Fight!
Fight... or die...!
Win... and live!
What the hell are you thinking, brat?!
The only way to win...
is to fight!
No... I can't do it!
Just then... I remembered.
I had seen this same thing...
...over and over...
...all my life.
I'd seen it everywhere I went...
But...
I always looked the other way.
"That's right...
We live...
...in a cruel world."
At that moment,
my body stopped shaking.
I was in full control of
myself after that.
I thought I could do anything...
"Fight."
"Fight!"
Stabbed through the heart from behind.
Those kids did this?
Eren. I told you to wait
at the foot of the mountain.
Do you have any idea what you've done?!
I got rid of some dangerous animals!
They just happened to look like people!
Eren!
They would've been long gone
by the time the Military Police arrived!
It would've been too late!
Even so, you were just lucky, Eren!
The way you casually threw
your life away is what I'm angry about!
But...
I wanted to save her as fast as I could...
Mikasa. Do you remember me?
We've met several times before,
when you were little.
Dr. Jaeger...
How do I get home from here?
I'm cold...
I have nowhere to go now...
You can keep this.
Warm, isn't it?
It is...
Mikasa.
Come live with us.
Huh?
You've been through a lot.
You need plenty of rest.
What is it?
C'mon. Let's go already.
To our home.
Yeah. Let's go...
A cruel world in which only
the victors are allowed to live...
Time to withdraw, Ackermann!
Let's scale the wall!
I'll go assist the vanguard's retreat!
H-Hey, Ackermann!
But I do have a place to
call home in this world now.
Eren.
As long as I have you,
I can do anything.
Your dreams are where your heart is
They're more fragile than life itself
Over and over you cast them aside,
only to find more
Now, rest in peace
Pounding impulses defile the things we wish for
and the more we forget
the more we remember again
In this beautiful, cruel world
all I can do is ask why we're still alive
Oh, with our strength... and our weakness...
what are we going to protect if there's no sense
to anything anymore?
"I have a place to call home."
After finishing her rearguard duties,
Mikasa hurries to see Eren,
only to learn of his death.
Small Blade: The Struggle for Trost, Part 3